LISA (ILSHIN) JI

Waterloo, Ontario N2K 4E2 ■ 226-505-7233 ■

PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES, REPOSITORY

• Portfolio: https://ilshin714.github.io/portfolio/

• LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/iji/

• GitHub: https://github.com/ilshin714

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software development professional with experience in developing and designing full stack web application using C#, Java, .NET, Spring Boot, SQL Server, MySQL, Blazor, HTML, CSS, React and JavaScript. Adept at developing and deploying complex backend systems, web services and databases.

SKILLS

- C#, Java
- MSSQL, MySQL, Oracle, MongoDB
- HTML, CSS, Figma, JavaScript, React, BootStrap
- Spring boot, ASP.NET, .NET 6, Restful API
- Agile using Azure, Jira, GitLab, and Git
- English, Korean, and Chinese
- Office Suite programs

WORK HISTORY

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER 05/2021 to 08/2022

Peer Group Inc

- Developed cloud-hosted ASP.NET Blazor Server web application with C#
- Worked with UX designers to gather details of UI/UX design before dev implementation
- Investigated and worked with Quality Assurance (QA) specialists to resolve issues
- Developed software code in compliance with Software Development standards
- Used Azure DevOps work item management system to keep tasks up-to-date

DEVELOPER / BUSINESS COORDINATOR 07/2020 to 12/2020

SubServe, Conestoga Venture Lab

- Developed admin site using Spring Boot and React
- Performed Coordinator duty by managing communication, market research, official presentation

BUSINESS ADMINISTRATOR 01/2015 to 03/2019

Kiban Tech, co., Ltd

- Analyzed market environments, developed business strategies and coordinated with relevant departments of the company to complete major key initiatives
- Collaborated with global clients including China, Canada, United States, Azerbaijan, etc.

PROJECT

IDEA INCUBATOR NETWORK PLATFORM 01/2023 to 04/2023

Conestoga College

- Live Site: https://ideaincubator.azurewebsites.net/
- Youtube: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fjfxdEGv4U0&list=PL9FhyXGSYnjVQ03FdzwywfvBlEf0nKsS_
- Repository: https://github.com/ilshin714/IdeaIncubator
- Developed Idea Sharing Network Platform with C#, .Net6, Blazor, MS SQL Server, and Azure DevOps
- Designed database schema and service Architecture
- Prototyped UI with Figma and implemented features as per each requirement

ORGANIC GREEN E-COMMERCE WEB APPLICATION 10/2019 to 11/2019

Joong-ang High Tech Advancement Academy

- Youtube: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jodzRugxWTA
- Repository: https://github.com/ilshin714/OrganicGreen_ShoppingMall_Java_Spring_Bootstrap_Oracle/tree/master
- Developed Online Shopping Application with Java, HTML5/CSS 3, JQuery, JavaScript, Ajax, Mybatis, Spring MVC, Bootstrap, Map API
- Designed Database schema, UI, Chart and Implemented content CRUD of Admin page

ONLINE BUSINESS WEB APPLICATION 05/2023 to PRESENT

Goen Japanese Restaurant

- Ongoing project
- Live Site: https://hae7404.wixsite.com/angelabrand
- Design web site flow and features with WIX and JavaScript

PLEASE CHECK MY PORTFOLIO TO SEE MORE PROJECTS: https://ilshin714.github.io/portfolio/

EDUCATION

Computer Programmer/Analyst (Co-op): Computer Analysis and Programming, **04/2023**

Conestoga College - Waterloo, ON

GPA: 3.98/4.0

Software Development Certification Course: 11/2019

Joong-ang High Tech Advancement Academy - South Korea

Bachelor of Arts: Economics/Chinese Studies, 08/2013

Hanyang University GPA: 4.07, GPA: 4.5